<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<titles>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Симеон Стълпник </bg>
      <en>Office for St. Symeon the Stylite</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Симеону Столпнику</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Тропар за св. Йоан Постник</bg>
      <en>Troparion for St. John the Faster</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Иоанну Постнику</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Антим</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Anthimos of Nikomedeia</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Антиму</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за Чудото на архангел Михаил в Хоня</bg>
      <en>Office for the Miracle of the Archangel Michael at Colossae</en>
      <ru>Служба о Чуде архангела Михаила в Хонех</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg> </bg>
      <en>Служба за св. Созонт и за Предпразненство на Рождство на пресвета Богородица </en>
      <ru>Office for the St. Sozon and the pre-feast of the Nativity of the Theotokos</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за Рождество на пресвета Богородица</bg>
      <en>Office for the Nativity of the Theotokos</en>
      <ru>Служба Рождеству пресвятой Богородицы</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири и тропар за св. Севериан и за поклонение на Кръста Господен</bg>
      <en>Stichera and troparia for St. Severianos and for the worship of the Holy Cross</en>
      <ru>Стихиры и тропари св. Севериану и на поклонение Креста Господня</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Теодора Александрийска</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Theodora of Alexandria</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Феодоре Александрийской</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Прохор и за Предпразненство на Въздвижение на Кръста Господен</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Prohor and for the pre-feast of the Exaltation of the Holy Cross</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Прохору и Предпразднству Воздвижения Креста Господня</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за Въздвижение на Кръста Господен</bg>
      <en>	Office for the Exaltation of the Holy Cross</en>
      <ru>	Служба на Воздвижение Креста Господня</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Никита </bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Niketas</en>
      <ru>	Стихира св. Никите</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Ефимия </bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Euphemia</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Евфимии</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Харалампий </bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Charalambos</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Харалампий</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Трофим и дружината му</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St Trophimos and companions</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Трофиму и дружине его</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Евстатий и семейството му</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Eustathios and Family</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Евстафию и его семьи</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Фока </bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Phokas</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Фоке</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Йоан Кръстител</bg>
      <en>Office for St. John the Baptist</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Иоанну Крестителю</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири и песнопение за св. Текла </bg>
      <en>Stichera and hymn for St. Thekla</en>
      <ru>Стихиры и песнопения св. Фекле</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Йоан Богослов</bg>
      <en>Office for St. John the Theologian</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Иоанну Богослову</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Харитон</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Chariton</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Харитону</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири и тропар за св. Григорий</bg>
      <en>Stichera and troparia for St. Gregory</en>
      <ru>Стихиры и тропари св. Григорию</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за св. апостол Ананий</bg>
      <en>Stichera for St. apostle Ananias</en>
      <ru>Стихиры св. апостолу Анании</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира и тропар за св. Киприан и Юстина</bg>
      <en>Stichera and troparion for St. Cyprian and Justina</en>
      <ru>Стихира и тропарь свв. Киприану и Иустине</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира и песнопение за св. Дионисий Ареопагит</bg>
      <en>Sticheron and hymn for St. Dionysios the Areopagite</en>
      <ru>Стихира и песнопение св. Дионисию Ареопагиту</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. апостол Тома</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Thomas Apostle</en>
      <ru>Служба св. апостолу Фоме</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири и тропари за св. Сергий и Вакх</bg>
      <en>Stichera and troparia for St. Sergios and Bacchos</en>
      <ru>Стихиры и тропари свв. Сергию и Вакху</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира на апостол Яков</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. James, son of Alpheus</en>
      <ru>Стихира апостолу Иакову</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира и тропар за светите отци на седмия събор в Никея</bg>
      <en>Sticheron and troparion for Holy Fathers at the Seventh council of Nicaea</en>
      <ru>Стихира и тропарь святым отцам седмого собора в Никеи</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за св. Пров, Тарх, Андроник, св. Анастасия и Евстатий епископ</bg>
      <en>Stichera for St. Probos, Tarachos and Andronikos, St. Anastasia and Eustathios</en>
      <ru>Стихиры св. Прову, Тарху, Андронику, св. Анастасии и Евстафию епископу</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Петка-Параскева</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Paraskeve</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Параскеви-Петки</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Лонгин</bg>
      <en>	Sticheron for St. Longinos</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Лонгину</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Иван Рилски</bg>
      <en>Office for St. John of Rila</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Иоанну Рыльскому</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Аверкий </bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Aberkios of Hierapolis</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Аверкию</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира и тропар за св. ап. Яков; св. Захарий и св. Симеон</bg>
      <en>Sticheron and troparion for St. James Adelphotheos, St. Zacharias and St. Simeon</en>
      <ru>Стихира и тропарь св. ап. Иакову; св. Захарии и св. Симеону</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Тропар за св. Арета и дружината му</bg>
      <en>Troparion for St. Arethas and companions</en>
      <ru>Тропарь св. Арефе</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира и тропар за св. Маркиан и други</bg>
      <en>Sticheron and troparion for St. Markianos and others</en>
      <ru>Стихира и тропарь св. Маркиану и другие</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Димитър Солунски</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Demetrios of Thessalonike</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Димитрию Солунскому</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Зиновий, св. Зиновия; св. Маркиан и св. Кирияк патриарх </bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Zenobios and Zenobia, and St. Markianos of Syracuse and St. Kyriakos the patriarch</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Зиновию, св. Зиновии; св. Маркиану и св. Кириаку патриарху</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. безсребърници Козма и Дамян</bg>
      <en>Office for Sts. unmercenary Kosmas and Damianos</en>
      <ru>Служба свв. безсребреникам Косме и Дамиану</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Акиндин и дружината му</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Akindynos and companions</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Акиндину и дружина его</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Йоаникий Велики</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Ioannikios the Great</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Иоанникию Великому</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Павел Изповедник и св. Александър, патриарх Цариградски</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Paul the Confessor and St. Alexander the patriarch of Constantinople</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Павлу Исповеднику и св. Александру, патриарху Цариградскому</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Песнопение за св. Антуса и родителите ѝ. Памет на св. апостол Яков</bg>
      <en>Hymn for St. Anthusa her parents and memory for St. James the Apostle</en>
      <ru>Песнопение св. Анфусе и ее родителей. Памят св. апостолу Иакову</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за събор на архангелите Михаил и Гавриил</bg>
      <en>Office for the the Synaxis of the Archangels Michael and Gabriel</en>
      <ru>Служба Собору архангелов Михаила и Гавриила</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за св. Мина, Викторий, Викентий, св. Иоан Милостиви, и Теодор Студит</bg>
      <en>Stichera for the Sts. Menas, Victor, Vikentios and St. John Eleemon, and Theodore of Stoudios</en>
      <ru>Стихиры св. Мине, Викторию, Викентию, Иоанну Милостивому и Феодору Студиту</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Йоан Златоуст</bg>
      <en>Office for St John Chrysostom</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Иоанну Златоусту</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. апостол Филип</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Philip the Apostle</en>
      <ru>Служба св. апостолу Филиппу</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. апостол Яков и св. Гурий, Самон и Авив</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. James the Apostle, and Gourias, Samonas and Abibos</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. апостолу Иакову и свв. Гурию, Самону и Авиву</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. апостол и евангелист Матей</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Matthew Evangelist the Apostle</en>
      <ru>Служба св. апостолу и евангелисту Мафею</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира и тропар за св. Григорий Чудотворец</bg>
      <en>Sticheron and troparion for St. Gregory Thaumaturge</en>
      <ru>Стихира и тропарь св. Григорию Чудотворцу</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Григорий Декаполит и Предпразненство на Въведение в храма на св. Богородица</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Gregory of Dekapolis and Forefeast of the Entry of the Theotokos into the Temple</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Григорию Декаполиту и Предпразненства Введения в храм св. Богородицы</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за Въведение Богородично</bg>
      <en>Office for the Entry of the Theotokos into the Temple</en>
      <ru>Служба Введения в храм св. Богородицы</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за св. Михаил войн</bg>
      <en>Stichera for Michael the Warrior</en>
      <ru>Стихиры св. Михаилу воину</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира и тропар за св. Климент папа Римски и св. Меркурий</bg>
      <en>Sticheron and troparion for St. Clement of Rome and St. Merkourios</en>
      <ru>Стихира и тропрь св. Клименту, папе Римскому и св. Меркурию</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Кoзма и Дамян и за св. Яков Персиец</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for Sts. Kosmas and Damianos and St. Jacob the Persian</en>
      <ru>Стихира свв. Козме и Дамиану и св. Иакову Персиянину</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири и тропар за св. апостол Андрей</bg>
      <en>Stichera and tropraion for St. Andrew</en>
      <ru>Стихиры и тропарь св. апостолу Андрею</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири и тропар за св. Ананий, св. пророк Наум и св. Теодор</bg>
      <en>Stichera and troparion for St. Ananias, St. Nahum the Apostle, and St. Theodor</en>
      <ru>Стихиры и тропарь св. Ананию, св. пророку Науму и св. Феодору</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Варвара, Йоан Дамаскин и св. Юлияния</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Barbara, John of Damascus and St. Juliana</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Варваре,  Иоанну Дамаскину и св. Иулиане</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Аверкий, св. Сава Освещни и св. Кръстина</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Aberkios, Sabas of the Great Lavra and St. Christina</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Аверкию, св. Савве Освященному и св. Кристине</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Никола Мирликийски</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Nicholas of Myra</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Николаю Мирликийскому</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за зачатие на св. Анна</bg>
      <en>Office for Conception of Anna, Mother of the Theotokos</en>
      <ru>Служба Зачатию св. Анны</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Даниил Стълпник и св. Стефан</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Daniel the Stylite</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Даниилу Столпнику и св. Стефану</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Спиридон</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Spyridon</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Спиридону</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за св. Евстратий, Авксентий, Евгений, Мардарий, Орест и св. Ликия</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for Sts. Auxentios, Eugenios, Mardarios, and Orestes and St. Lucia</en>
      <ru>Стихиры свв. Евстратию, Авксентию, Евгению, Мардарию и Оресту и св. Лукии</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Тропар за св. Тирс, Левкий и Калиник</bg>
      <en>Troparion for St. Thyrsos, Leukios and companions</en>
      <ru>Тропарь свв. Фирсу, Левкию и Каллинику</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за св. Мемиос, Модест и Пров</bg>
      <en>Stichera for St. Memnon, Modestos of Jerusalem and Probos</en>
      <ru>Стихиры св. Мемнону, Модесту Иерусалимскому и Прову</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за тримата отроци Ананий, Азарий и Мисаил и пророк Даниил.</bg>
      <en>Office for Sts. Hananiah, Azariah and Mishael (Three Holy Children) and for St. Daniel the Prophet</en>
      <ru>Служба трем отрокам Ананию, Азарию и Мисаилу и пророку Даниилу</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Бонифаций и Предпразненство на Рождество Христово</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Bonifatios and Forefeasts of the Birth of Christ</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Вонифатию и Предпразненству Рождества Христова</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Игнатий Богоносец и Предпразненство на Рождество Христово</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Ignatios Theophoros and Forefeasts of the Birth of Christ</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Игнатию Богоносцу  и Предпразненству Рождества Христова</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Евиот, св. Юлияния и Предпразненство Рождество Христово</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Eubiotus, martyr at Cyzicus in Bithynia, St. Juliana of Nicomedia and Forefeasts of the Birth of Christ </en>
      <ru>Служба св. Евиота, св. Иулиании  и Предпразненству Рождества Христова</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Анастасия и Предпразненство на Рождество Христово</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Anastasia the Widowand Forefeasts of the Birth of Christ</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Анастасии  и Предпразненству Рождества Христова</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за освещаване на храма „Св. София” в Константинопол, св. Нифонт, св. десет мъченици от Крит, св. Богородица и Предпразненство на Рождество Христово</bg>
      <en>Office for the Sanctuary of the temple "St. Sofia" in Constantinople, St. Nephon, Ten Martyrs of Crete, for Theotokos and Forefeasts of the Birth of Christ</en>
      <ru>Служба Освещения храма Св. Софии в Константинополе, св. Нифонту, десятим святых критских мучеников и Предпразненству Рождества Христова</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Евгения и Предпразненство на Рождество Христово</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Eugenia and Forefeasts of the Birth of Christ</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Евгении и Предпразненству Рождества Христова</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Чинопоследование на часовете</bg>
      <en>Rite for the hours creation</en>
      <ru>Чинопоследование часов</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за Рождество Христово</bg>
      <en>Office for the Birth of Christ</en>
      <ru>Служба Рождеству Христову</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. първомъченик Стефан</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Stephen the First Martyr</en>
      <ru>Служба св. первомученику Стефану</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Тропар за св. Маркел, Теодор и Стефан Чудотворец</bg>
      <en>Troparion for St. Markellos the Akoimetos, Theodore and Stephen the Thaumaturge</en>
      <ru>Тропарь свв. Маркеллу, Феодору и Стефану Чудотворцу</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за св. младенци, избити от Ирод във Витлеем и преподобни Маркел</bg>
      <en>Stichera for the young children killed by Herod in Bethlehem and for St. Markellos</en>
      <ru>Стихиры святым младенцам, избиенным от Ирода во Вифлееме и преподобному  Маркеллу</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за св. Василий Велики</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Basil the Great</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Василию Великому</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Зотик и св. Силвестър, папа Римски</bg>
      <en>	Office for St. Zotikos of Rome and St. Silvester I Pope</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Зотику св. Сильвестру, папе Римскому</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Гордий, Исидор, св. Силвестър, папа Римски и Предпразненство на Богоявление</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Gordios, Isidore of Pelousion, Silvester I Pope and Forefeasts of Theophany</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Гордию, Исидору, св. Сильвестру, папе Римскому и Предпразненства Богоявления</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. пророк Малахий и св. Гордий и Предпразненство на Богоявление</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Malachias and St. Gordios and Forefeasts of Theophany</en>
      <ru>Служба св. пророку Малахии и св. Гордию и Предпразненства Богоявления</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Теопист, Теона, Зосима, Атанасий и Теоктист и Предпразненство на Богоявление</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Theopemptos and Theonas, Zosimos, Athanasios and Theoktistos and Forefeasts of Theophany</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Феописту, Феоне, Зосиме, Афанасию и Феоктисту и Предпразненства Богоявления</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за Предпразенство на Богоявление</bg>
      <en>Office for Forefeasts of Theophany</en>
      <ru>Служба Предпразненства Богоявления</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Навечерие на Богоявление</bg>
      <en>The vigil of Theophany</en>
      <ru>Навечерие Богоявления</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за събор на св. Йоан Кръстител</bg>
      <en>Office for the the Synaxis до St. John the Baptist</en>
      <ru>Служба Собору св. Иоанна Кретителя</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Евгений и Св. Богородица</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Eugenian and Theotokos</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Евгению и св. Богородици </ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Григорий Нисийски</bg>
      <en>	Sticheron for St. Gregory of Nyssa</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Григорию Нисскому</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за св. Маркел, Теодосий и мъченик Петър</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Markellos, Theodosios Koinobiarches and Peter the martyr</en>
      <ru>Стихиры св. Маркеллу, Феодосию и мученику Петру</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за св. Маркел и св. отци, избити на планината Синай</bg>
      <en>Stichera for St. Markellos and for Abbades killed in the Mount Sinai</en>
      <ru>Стихиры св. Маркеллу и святым отцам в Синае избиенных</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Картерий, Василий, Павел Тивейски и Йоан Колибник</bg>
      <en>Stichera for St. Carterius, St. Basil, St. Paul the Hermit and John Kalybites</en>
      <ru>Стихира свв. Картерию, Василию, Павлу Тивейскому и Иоанну Кущнику</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири и тропар за поклонение на честните вериги на св. апостол Петър и св. Павел Тивейски</bg>
      <en>Sticheron and troparion for the Veneration of the Honorable Chains of St. Peter the Apostle and St. Paul of Thebes</en>
      <ru>Стихиры и тропарь на поклонение честным веригам св. апостолу Петру и св. Павел Фивейский</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири и тропар за св. Антоний Велики</bg>
      <en>Stichera and troparion for St. Antony the Great</en>
      <ru>Стихиры и тропарь св. Антонию Великому</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири и тропар за св. Атанасий и Кирил Александрийски</bg>
      <en>	Stichera and troparion for St. Athanasios and Cyril of Alexandria</en>
      <ru>Стихиры и тропарь св. Афанасию и Кириллу Александрийскому</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири и песнопение за св. апостол Тимотей, и мъченици Виктор и Викентий</bg>
      <en>	Sticheron and hymn for St. Timotheos the Apostle and martyres St. Victor and Companions</en>
      <ru>	Стихиры и песнопение св. апостолу Тимофею и мученикам Виктору и Викентию</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири и тропар за св. Григорий Богослов</bg>
      <en>Stichera and troparion for St. Gregory of Nazianzos</en>
      <ru>Стихиры и тропарь св. Григорию Богослову</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Песнопение за връщане на мощите на св. Теодор Студит и памет на архангел Гавраил</bg>
      <en>Hymn for the transfer of the relics of St. Theodore the Studite from Akritian Cherson to Constantinople and memory for Gabriel archangel</en>
      <ru>Песнопение на перенесение мощей св. Феодора Студита и память архангелу Михаилу</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за пренасяне на мощите на св. Йоан Златоуст и св. Матрона</bg>
      <en>Stichera for the translation of relics of St. John Chrysostom and St. Matrona</en>
      <ru>Стихиры на перенесение мощей св. Иоанна Златоуста и св. Матроны</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Ефрем Сирин</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Ephrem the Syrian</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Ефрему Сирину</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Яков и пренасяне мощите на св. Игнатий Богоносец</bg>
      <en>	Office for St. James and translation of the relics of St. Ignatios Theophoros</en>
      <ru>	Служба св. Иакову и на перенесение мощей св. Игнатия Богоносца</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за пренасяне мощите на св. Климент Римски и памет на св. цар Петър Български</bg>
      <en>	Office for the translation of the relics of St. Clement of Rome and the memory of St. Peter, Tsar of Bulgara</en>
      <ru>	Служба на перенесение мощей св. Климента Ромского и память св. Петра, царя Болгарского</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири и тропар за св. Кир и Йоан</bg>
      <en>Stichera and troparion for St. Kyros and John</en>
      <ru>Стихиры и тропарь св. Киру и Иоанну</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Трифон и Предпразненство на Сретение Господне</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Tryphon and the Forefeasts of the Candlemas</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Трифону и предпразднства Сретения Господня</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>	</bg>
      <en>Служба за св. Симеон Богоприимец</en>
      <ru>Office for the St. Symeon Theodochos</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Власий</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Blasios</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Власию</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Тропар за св. Марут и мъчениците, пострадали с него в Мартиропол</bg>
      <en>Troparion for St. Maruthas and the martyrs in Martyropolis</en>
      <ru>Тропарь св. Маруфу и мученикам, пострадавшим с ним в Мартирополе</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за намиране главата на Йоан Кръстител</bg>
      <en>Office for the Finding of the Head of St. John the Baptist</en>
      <ru>Служба на обретение главы Иоанна Крестителя</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Евдокия, Маркел, Андоний, Нестор и Трофим</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Eudokia of Heliopolis, Martyr Marcellus, Anthony from Siria, Martyrs Nestor and Tribiminus</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Евдокии, Маркеллу, Антонию, Нестору и Трофиму</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Конон и св. 42-ма аморийски мъченици</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Konon and for Forty-Two Martyrs of Amorion</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Конону Исаврийскому и св. 42 мученикам аморийским</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. 40 Севастийски мъченици</bg>
      <en>Office for Sts. 40 Holy Martyrs of Sebaste</en>
      <ru>Служба свв. 40 мученикам Севастийским</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за Благовещение</bg>
      <en>Office for Annunciation</en>
      <ru>Служба на Благовещение</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Георги Победоносец</bg>
      <en>Office for St. George Great Martyr</en>
      <ru>Служба Георгию Победоносцу</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. апостол и евангелист Маркo</bg>
      <en>Office for St Mark the Apostle</en>
      <ru>Служба св. апостолу и евангелисту Марка</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Тропар за св. Василий, Помпилий, Евлогий, Дадий и Клитиник</bg>
      <en>Troparion for St. Basil, Bishop of Amasea and St. Terence and his companions</en>
      <ru>Тропарь св. Василию, Помпилию, Евлогию, Дадию и Клитику</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за св. апостол Яков Зеведеев, св. епископ Патрикий и св. Ефрем</bg>
      <en>Stichera for St. James the Apostle, the son of Zebedee, Patrikios and companions, St. Ephrem</en>
      <ru>Стихиры св. апостолу Иакову Зеведееву, св. епископу Патрикию и св. Ефрему</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. пророк Йеремия</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Jeremiah the Prophet</en>
      <ru>Служба св. пророку Иеремии</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Йоан Богослов и св. Арсений</bg>
      <en>Office for St. John the Theologian and St. Arsenios the Great</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Иоанну Богослову и св. Арсению</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Епифаний Кипърски и св. Герман Константинополски</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Epiphanios of Cyprus and St. Germanos I Patriarch</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Епифанию Кипрскому и св. Герману Констанинопольскому</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Ахил Лариски, апостол Юда, Пахомий Велики и епископ Авдик</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Achilles, Bishop of Larissa, Pachomios the Great and Abdikas</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Ахиху Ларисскому, апостолу Иуде, Пахомию Великому и епископу Авдику</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Константин и Елена</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Constantine the Great and Helena</en>
      <ru>Служба свв. Константину и Елене</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Симеон Стълпник и майка му Марта, мъчениците Мелентион и Стефан и други</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Simeon the Stylite, and his motehr Martha, Meletius the General, Stephen and companions</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Симеону Столпнику, его матери Марфе, мученикам Мелентиону и Стефану и другие </ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за св. Никифор Цариградски, св. Герман и Еразъм</bg>
      <en>Stichera for St. Nikephoros I Patriarch, St. Germanos I Patriarch and Erasmus</en>
      <ru>Стихиры св. Никифору Цариградскому, св. Герману и Еразму</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Тропар за св. Митрофан патриарх Константинополски</bg>
      <en>Troparion for St. Metrophanes Patriarch of Constantinople</en>
      <ru>Тропарь св. Митрофану, патриарху Константинополя</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Теодор Стратилат</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Theodore Stratelates</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Феодору Стратилату</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. апостоли Вартоломей и Варнава</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Bartholomew and St. Barnabas</en>
      <ru>Служба св. апостолам Варфоломею и Варнаве</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Онуфрий Пустинник и св. Трифон</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Onouphrios and St. Tryphon</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Онуфрию и св. Трифону</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. пророк Елисей</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Elisaios</en>
      <ru>Служба св. пророку Елисею</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за рождението на св. Йоан Кръстител</bg>
      <en>Office for Birth of St. John the Baptist</en>
      <ru>Служба рождению св. Иоанна Крестителя</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за апостолите Петър и Павел</bg>
      <en>Office for Sts. Peter and Paul the Apostles</en>
      <ru>Служба апостолам Петру и Павлу</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. безсребърници Козма и Дамян</bg>
      <en>Office for Sts. Kosmas and Damianos for</en>
      <ru>Служба свв. бессребреникам Косме и Дамиану</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за полагане ризата и пояса на пресвета Богородица</bg>
      <en>Office for the Deposition of the Robe of Theotokos in the Blachernai Church</en>
      <ru>Служба на положение Честной ризы и пояса пресвятой Богородицы во Влахерне</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Прокопий, Евстатий и Поликарп</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Prokopios megalomartyr, St. Eustathios and St. Polykarpos of Smyrna</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Прокопию, Евстафию и Поликарпу</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихира за св. Маркиан</bg>
      <en>Sticheron for St. Markianos</en>
      <ru>Стихира св. Маркиану</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Кирик и Юлита</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Kerykos and Julitta</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Кирику и Иулитте</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Афиноген и св. Марина</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Athenogenes and St. Marina</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Афиногену и св. Марине</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. пророк Илия и св. пророк Елисей</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Elijah the Prophet and St. Elisaios</en>
      <ru>Служба св. пророку Илии св. пророку Елисею</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири и тропар за св. Мария Магдалена, св. Фока и св. Елена</bg>
      <en>Stichera and troparion for St. Mary Magdalene, for St. Phokas and Helena</en>
      <ru>Стихира и тропарь св. Марии Магдалены, св. Фоке и св. Елене</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за св. Христина</bg>
      <en>Stichera for St. Christina</en>
      <ru>Стихиры св. Христине</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Стихири за св. Анна и св. Евпраксия</bg>
      <en>Stichera for St. Anna and St. Eupraxia</en>
      <ru>Стихиры св. Анне и св. Евпраксии</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Пантелеймон</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Panteleemon</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Панталеймону</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Макавеи</bg>
      <en>Office for the Holy Seven Maccabees</en>
      <ru>Служба свв. Маккавеям</ru>
   </title>
   <title>
      <bg>Служба за св. Евсигний и Тутаил  и Предпразненство на Преображение Господне</bg>
      <en>Office for St. Eusignius and Thuthael and Forefeast of the Transfiguration of our Lord</en>
      <ru>Служба св. Евсигнию и Тутаила; Предпразднство Преображения Господня</ru>
   </title>
</titles>
